# George Rezmikov

# UI/UX Designer

**PHONE** 8 (903) 215-21-90

**E-MAIL** georgeowlson@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO website link

@GeorgeOwlson

georgereznikov

georgereowlson

## Education

YANDEX PRACTICUM UX/UI DESIGNER

JANUARY 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

SCREAM SCHOOL MOTION GRAPHIC DESIGN

SEPTEMBER 2019 - FEBRUARY 2019

**BACHELOR OF ARTS, MGUSIT** 

2003 - 2008 MOSCOW, RUSSIA

## Skills

FIGMA	9/10
PHOTOSHOP	9/10
ILLUSTRATOR	8/10
INDESIGN	6/10
AFTER EFFECTS	4/10

## **About**

My name is George. I'm a multidisciplinary designer with 8 years of experience and a particular interest in UI/UX design. Throughout my career, I have worked with big brands such as Coca-Cola, Fanta, Sprite, Nissan, HP, Adidas, McDonalds. During my time at TBWA our team was awarded two Bronze Cannes Lions in Print Outdoor и Art Direction.

# Work experience

#### FC LOKOMOTIV MOSCOW / ART DIRECTOR

JULY 2021 - APRIL 2022

 designed visual identity and its graphic elements (social media, outdoor advertising, prints, stadium navigation) 

- designed a loyalty program website (logo and identity creation, UX copywriting)
- · collaborated with a product marketing team to achieve higher results
- developed design concepts and its further scaling
- created motion graphics for (the football club's video channel) Loko TV

### TBWA MOSCOW / CREATIVE DESIGNER

APRIL 2018 - JULY 2021

- developed creative design concepts to clients (Alcon, Nissan, HP, Adidas, Gazprom)
- designed visual content: key visuals, car retouching, landing pages, websites
- · created motion design for cases and internal projects
- · created and edited Power Point/Keynote presentations for clients
- · mentored and instructed interns

#### THE DIRECTORS / DESIGNER

APRIL 2015 - APRIL 2018

- was promoted within a six-month timeframe for exceeding goals
- · designed original graphics for 33 Fanta Mini Apps on VK.com
- ideated and produced visual content for Sprite and Semper on social media platforms
- designed a website encyclopedia for Semper and its products
- created a special project website for Coca-Cola and designed limited edition cans for the rock/pop/hip-hop summer campaign
- · designed the layout of print collateral: brochures, flyers, banners, etc.